it's week two of me trying to turn $100
into a million day
trp last week was week one let me tell
you all about it so last week was the
start of the 100 to the mill Challenge
and the goal was to take $100 to $200
last week and we almost blew the account
on our first position that we entered
because the trade went straight into our
stop loss the account is not looking
that good right now you guys can see
that we're currently down about $32 on
the account
but we ended up turning the $100 into
$437 with one single trade so we outdid
the goal for last week because the goal
for this week was to take the $200 that
we would have made last week to then
$400 this week now this week since we're
starting with
$437 the goal is to take $437 to $900 by
the end of this
week because the goal of the challenge
is to double up every single week so
this week is 400 to 900 the next week is
9900 to 1,800 1,800 to 36 so on until we
turn $100 to a million day trade so with
that being said let the challenge
begin good morning ladies and gentlemen
welcome to week number two training $100
into a million today it's late caught us
late this morning it is Monday morning
at 11: in the morning usually I would do
this at 9:00 a.m. but honestly all
morning I've just been looking at the
charts potentially about enter your
trade and we just opened the brand new
Instagram account where I'm going to be
doing daily updates on the trades that
I'm going to be taking and this account
is named 10 121m so if you guys want to
go see updates on the type of Trades
that I'm taking aside from YouTube here
after it happens go follow that account
with that being said we got I think
seven solid markets in the markets seven
solid markets in the markets it's a lot
of markets a lot of [__] money that's
what I'm talking about but before I get
started oh [__] let me show you guys the
my Facebook account like always and let
me show you guys the metat trador just
so you guys can see stting balance of
the account so right now account is
still on
$437 and you guys can see here on the my
effects book it is the exact same thing
$437 188 as of right now 11:00 a.m.
Monday morning no trades have been taken
let me show you guys let's start off
with USD JPY so USD JPY has a very clean
left head kind of right shoulder action
going around here we broke the neckline
now we are retesting the neckline of The
Head and Shoulders
along with the 1H hour EMA 4H hour time
frame looks absolutely phenomenal we're
having a beautiful 1H hour bearish
engulfing Candlestick looks like we're
having that pullback to retest that
previous structure level and then the
daily time frame does not get any
cleaner than this daily previous
structure level daily EMA and then you
guys can look left it is obviously a
level of resistance whenever we're under
a level resistance whatever we're under
and this line right here what is it you
may be asking around psychological level
1575 we or like the smart money concept
guys would call it an order block potato
potato this is a round pychological
level within area of Interest so this
trade is my number one trade that I'm
going to be interested in taking this
week all I'm really waiting for on this
market so earlier this week what I was
waiting for was this break so that break
already happened and now this pullback
is actively happening so I just got to
wait for price to go back into this area
so I can actually enter this trade I
analyzed this yesterday with the
students on Sunday swings but obviously
it paid out a lot faster I was literally
as I analyze the markets I'm like you
know what I'm not going to start the
YouTube series into tomorrow and then
literally in the night time it played
out so I might have to start these
series on Sunday as soon as I get off
the call with the students but with that
being said the next Market is
gbpusd so gbpusd was the market that we
were actually looking to trade last week
so last week you guys can tell that we
were in this bullish market right here
we had the break and then on this ret
test right here we did not find an entry
so price continued to head to the
downside but then we officially had the
retest as we've been looking for it for
this level and then the daily time frame
is where it actually starts looking
clean because you can see the shift in
the market so the daily time frame you
can see how this is a beautiful higher
low higher high we broke it now I'm
waiting for price to come back and then
retest that area of interest and that
structure point so literally all I'm
waiting for on this Market is for it to
actually just pull up into this area so
I can execute the trade cuz again this
area of Interest also has a round
psychological level 1.
29500 so this is a very key area where
we should be selling I could sell right
here but I would just have to have my
stop loss really big and then that'll
just make the risk to reward ratio not
make any sense the risk reward ratio has
to be a minimum of a 1 to2 so as of
right now we got to be very patient as
we wait for this trade to pull back to
this area to enter the market next
Market is going to be GB P CHF so a
quick actual fun fact about GBP CHF it
is probably my favorite pair and my most
OG pair gbpchf is the market that made
me the trader that I am today because I
caught a really nice bull run back in
2021 as soon as you know Co was
finishing and literally this was the
pair that made me realize to trade with
the trend and trade with Rift management
RI RI Rift management Rift management
the point is I haven't traded this
Market since then because just hasn't
been giving me great opportunities and
I've been trying to enter a trade on it
but I haven't been able to find one and
I think this might be the one so as you
guys can see right here daily time frame
we are clearly having a rejection from
this resistance resistance and then
resistance level where now we could be
holding it as support you go down to
then the 4H hour time frame and the 4our
time frame you can see this is a strong
level of resistance through here
resistance through here we're just
waiting for a quick break retest so then
we can head to the upside so this is an
accumulation or uh consolidation an
inverted Head and Shoulders whatever you
want to call it it's price stopping at
the strong level of support and
resistance now the only way we can take
it is once we have the confirmation of
the break and retest it's going to be
the break and retest of this neck line
of The Head and Shoulders break and
retest of that EMA break and retest of
this area of interest and break and
retest of this round psychological level
1.500 probably one of my favorite trades
as well for this week so those are three
very high high probability trade setups
this next trade setup I already played
out and that is GBP JPY so last week the
first trade that we took on the 100 to
the mail account was this one on GBP JPY
where this trade turned the $100 into
$437 and then on the next entry we're
waiting for this retest to them sell
which the retest didn't happen as the
area that I wanted to we missed it by
about 30 to 50 Pips and then the trade
headed to the downside so this trade is
pretty much gone the trade setup never
really gave the entry and we just missed
it but you can see here on the daily
time frame that it is very clear the
break and then the retest for the trade
to go to the downside once again
retesting round psychological level
24. but this trade was missed so we
didn't take it last but not least on the
trades that I'm interested for this week
that could happen kind of fast it's
going to be Euro GBP so eurogbp is
actually a followup from last week's
Challenge Series as well last week we
were looking to enter the trade right
around this area if we had this as a 4H
hour bearish and golfing Candlestick
which we did not so then this week I'm
going to be waiting for this break and
retest for price to then head to the
downside something that I could also
wait for is this little left head and
then a potential right shoulder to play
out right here then all we would do is
wait for then the retest of the neckline
of The Head and Shoulder so then we can
take the trade to the downside so as of
right now we have about four to five
really really good Market Sal ons that I
have are not that great not going to
confuse you guys but all I am going to
say is the one that I'm pretty much
almost ready to enter is going to be USD
JPY as soon as we pull up to this little
area of Interest right here so as of
right now it is currently 11:14 in the
morning Monday morning so s and forget
see where today takes us and if we end
up entering this Market all right guys
trade update it is currently 6:30 in the
afternoon literally haven't done
anything today haven't left the house
weather is ass it is currently hurricane
season in Miami so there's literally
like a storm going down earlier and
couldn't really do anything so just been
home all day but the market is about to
give us an entry on this trade so let me
show you guys so this is USD JPY we're
having the pull back exactly how I
wanted to right to that area of Interest
right to that EMA to then reject the
neckline of The Head and Shoulders
reject the area of interest and you have
that 1 hour bearish and golfing
Candlestick I love how the daily
Candlestick close with a beautiful like
look how beautiful that daily bearish
Eng golfing Candlestick is and tomorrow
we'll probably going to fill that Wick
so this is a very very good trade setup
where I'm be interested in taking this
trade very soon I'd say within the next
hour or two like obviously right now
we're not in the trade just show you
guys met a Trader we are still outside
of the trade but this sh looks very very
solid so this is just USD JPY which I
might take tonight next is going to be
gbpusd so gbpusd we are anticipating for
Price get back into this area so that we
can actually take the trade so we
started doing that already started
having the pool back into that area and
we're on the way there pretty much just
set and forgetting till price gets to
this point GBP CHF we were ant
anticipating for price to have a break
and then a retest so right now we're
having that break and the daily time
frame has had that bullish Eng gulfy
exactly how I anticipated and then euro
gvp is currently having that daily
bearish Candlestick we didn't have the
engulfing how I wanted to but we did
have this type of rejection from this
area which is good I'm still waiting for
this break and retest for us to enter
the cell but GBP CHF is playing out
perfectly USD JPY we're about to enter
this and then GBP USD had the pull back
to the area just waiting for a little
bit more with pullback so we so so
Market are doing exactly what we are
anticipating it's been a very slow and
boring day probably go hit the gym later
um hopefully I can get one of my cars
back today either my rollsroyce or my
Urus I get it back today they're both in
the shop and the Canon where's the Canon
H dude that's right the Canam the boat's
done though at least we got that the
boat's good I don't forget
yo
oh [__] with me huh [__] with me
literally usdjpy as simple and as
effective as I look at this [__] we
literally had the retest perfectly to
the area of Interest the Maru tweezer
top rejection bearish engulfing
Candlestick I keep telling you you need
an engulfing Candlestick to enter a TH
or a bullish engulfing to they by I'm
laughing cuz the mic is moving so the
point is that we're in this trade right
now literally we already at
$550 if this [__] hits that takeprofit
we'll probably be at like 2 3K it will
probably even break the goal for the
week that we've been anticipating so for
now just going
to so don't forget we literally full
margin this trade I don't know how they
allowed us to put 2.0 cuz I'm using a 1
to 500 leverage I was literally like I
maxed out the average I got really
really good spread GBP USD has still yet
to make it to this pullback right here
of this level to then so and GBP CHF has
not had the break and retest for us to
buy and Euro GBP has not had the break
and retest USD JPY is pretty much the
only trade so this trade can either
literally make us or break us it is
currently 8:00 p.m. Miami time so I
think it's like about 2 hours or an hour
and a half from the last time I updated
you guys and S and forget now what we're
going to go do is pick up Jordan so
Jordan and obviously you know it's
battling cancer and stuff and his legs
get really really swollen and I have a
cold plunge so cold water helps with
inflammation we're going to put him
inside the C plune in about like 20 30
minutes so we're going to pick him up
now and show you guys the whole drink
all right so this Jordan we're going to
take him out to the C plunge it's going
to suck bro it's going to suck it's cold
right it's cold plung dude it's going to
[__] suck but I'm telling you you're
going to get out you're going to feel
[__] amazing all right now I'm done
it's Clos you're ready to go yeah this
is your birthday gift actually this is
my birthday gift no that's your birthday
that's my gift yeah
I told you I got you in just came a
little late oh
[__] I never really get gifts I'm always
the guy gifting
[__] oh
[__] no way signed by the
[Music]
bo Mike Tyson you feel me one of the
best holy [__] bro this actually ganger
on this like the verification code in
the back the yeah the authenticity holy
[__] wow this is [__] gangster bro
authentification for Wow yo appreciate
you the best box for
best this actually [__] gangster I
know exactly where I'm going put it too
and then this right here is the you like
yeah it's actually super fire so you can
tell it it's legit Mike Tyson sign
memorability
fire so I forget super fire fire
apprciate appreciate you hope you like
all right this do it now I'm going throw
you in the cop plch all yeah all right
you ready yeah yeah is this high risk
right here I got you all right
how up
[Music]
so just picked to the boy Jordan right
now got him in the back taking him to my
house to do the cold plunge are you
ready yeah I'm ready I appreciate you
bro trust me of course brother of course
my legs are are killing me right now n
no you're good bro it's going to
definitely help it's going to suck at
the beginning but it'll help all right
take off the brakes here
peace good
[Music]
all right so how are we supposed to do
this see this is why I got to get richer
bro I don't have a [__] elevator dude
I feel like a [__] sorry D I don't have
an elevator sorry we're going to carry
you up next house we have an elevator at
fact 100% oh we are the elevator we are
the elevator today so enjoy this scene
of us very smoothly taking Jordan up the
[Music]
stairs hold up hold up let give mind
it's you want it no no no
on there bro my ass my ass feels cold as
[__] is your ass you're good n I'm I'm
trying to like get more like just wet
myself so I'm going side by
side yeah cold as [__]
[Music]
it's just like so annoying having to
like you think about it like like
imagine you're you don't well you don't
think about it but like imagine all the
[__] that you do on a day-to-day basis
like you do it and you don't realize
that you're doing it by yourself so like
when you have to have someone do it for
you it's like yeah
[__] fat as hell look at this [__]
[Music]
what's up all right see you tomorrow y
thank you bro trust me you don't know
how much I appreciate that like for real
I appreciate it course trust me you're
going to feel better the more you do it
this this looks
trade trade update oh [__] trade oh [__]
where's the phone all right guys Market
open and it's currently Tuesday Morning
8:26 in the morning and currently how
we're looking on this trade is we are up
about
$840,000
$850,000 so this trade has actually
played out very very very well you guys
can check out it's funny because I'm
surpassing to go every single week
without doing any more effort this is
going a lot better than the last
challenge so you guys can see right here
the entry that we had yesterday pretty
much predicted the push last night where
we were was kind of at this Candlestick
pretty much having a pullback throughout
all of London session this whole entire
Market had the push to the downside
when we were at this point right here we
were probably up about $2,000 but
obviously price has had a retracement to
this area where it's actually my
realistic takeprofit cuz I'm supposed to
be risking one to get about two but I'm
trying to stretch it out and get about a
3.4 so this Market is looking absolutely
beautiful on the 4H hour having very
strong bearish momentum and then the
daily time frame is having very very
strong bearish momentum I'm going to
wait if this daily Candlestick closes
under this line right here I can legit
have this Market go all the way down to
potentially areas like this over here so
to retest this previous structure level
if this daily Candlestick body closes
under that line right there if it closes
under then we can have the movement all
the way to the downside so USD
JPY just to show you guys once again
currently moving very very very nicely
into profit about
$840 of profit which our goal for this
week was to have a total Equity or
balance of about $800 $900 so we are
about to double that and it's looking
very nice I'm not looking to enter
potentially another position you guys
can see right here gvp USD we've
actually had the retracement somewhat to
the area of Interest where we were
looking to sell but price did not quite
make it there so we couldn't enter the
trade even if price did make it there I
would have not entered the trade cuz I'm
already in a winning one there's no
reason why to add risk if you're already
in a winning position but this shows you
guys that the set and forget strategy
and the market analysis is correct then
you have
gbpchf which is having the break and
retest perfectly as we've been
anticipating kind of sucks that I
couldn't couldn't trade this because I
already in USD JPY but once again just
confirms that the strategy is working
and then EUR GBP is literally doing
exactly what we mentioned yesterday it's
having the break it's going to then have
the retest to then head to the downside
this is literally as textbook as perfect
as it gets we haven't missed so we're
four for four five for five for this
week every single trade that we've
analyzed has played out which is [__]
crazy and all you really only need to do
is catch one you don't need to catch all
of them kind of impossible you catch all
of them there's no need all you really
need is one good one when you can up
your wrist just a little bit and then
you set and [__] forget all right so
curing up
$837 can't make this [__] up boys it's
crazy we might actually hit the [__]
million dollars we we really might
[__] do it this time bro and you're
surprised um bro cuz we're so ahead of
schedule we should be by the end of this
week at
$400 dude we're like on week five
already and it's week
two Dam this is going a little quicker
than a little it's going a little more s
and forget than I thought so now I have
to go to the dentist I'll probably take
you guys with me take a little video
have to go to the dentist after the
dentist come straight back and update
you guys again on what the Market's
going to do so stay tuned set for
[Music]
[Applause]
all right so today we're taking oh my
God M3 if you guys have ever been in a
beamer you guys know this thing here
gets all [__] sticky trade update
we're currently up about 1,00 so we're
doing very very well today we get the
Urus back so I have a wide body Urus pop
it
up yeah I haven't had the Urus for about
a month because I landed to one of my
friends and he broke the rear brake
caliper so it was getting fixed so I get
the Urus back today finally so I don't
have to drive neither of these cars for
a while and then Thursday so 2 days from
now I should get the Phantom back and
then the Porsche is in the [__] shop
fixing the clutch cuz I blew the
[Music]
transmission I personally don't think
the transmission should have ever broken
I don't think I did anything
wrong look that's literally a cop right
there right watch watch this
the
L when you're a profitable Trader the
law just doesn't apply to you
bro did you see that it was a cop
yeah that guy just watched and kept on
going with his day bro like when
honestly if I was a cop and I hear
somebody do that and I'm in a [__]
truck I'll be like have a good day bro
like you're not going to get him yeah
dude I'm I'm a menace sometimes in the
streets with these [__] cars and that
was a really good drift too
[Music]
all all right guys so trade update we
just left the gym right now trade update
is currently 12:30 in the afternoon so
like I mentioned earlier if that daily
Candlestick closes under that previous
structure level we're pretty much going
to set and forget this [__] for a very
long time 4 hours looking good we are
now currently up about $1,200 on the
account so I'm going to continue to set
them foret all right guys straight
update it is currently 317 in the
afternoon and we are up about 1,600 on
the trade and you guys you guys can see
here that the market is about to close
you guys can see that the market is
about to close in 2 hours so this daily
Candlestick will close about an hour 42
minutes and it's honestly going a lot
faster than I anticipated and we're
definitely going to close under that
previous structure level this is why you
set and forget your take profit you
never put a take profit you always put a
stop loss to minimize your losses you
never put a take profit you never want
to minimize your losses so this trade we
just continue to hold and so don't
forget so as right now we just got the
Urus back haven't had it for like a
month and a half so actually what
happened to it is that this rear brake
caliper broke this rear brake caliper
right here broke and all the oil from
the oil lines leaked and you can see
inside here how it's still like dirty
full of oil you see how it got back here
in this rear fender and it kind of like
rusted all this or whatever because I
just didn't want to fix it I broke it
the oil started leaking and I got to the
point where it stopped breaking cuz I
ran out of brake fluid and that's that's
where I'm like all right I got to go fix
it now I was literally breaking hitting
the break and it was not breaking there
was no oil to it you see a
light that does not look
safe a we're fine we're fine always
every single time you're going to H last
than yours you have to do
this course up so you hear the pops you
think they can hear
it there we go
there we going to head little 20 roll
let have a quick trade update right now
at 100 m
hour all right trade update
is Curr we're currently up about 100
1,600 so we have to hit 160 mph all
right ready I don't think we have enough
space yeah we don't we don't have enough
space Oh bro you want you want to know
how stupid I am bro that I didn't even
test if the brakes
worked well they work all right well
they work I'll tell you that right now
we literally haven't been driving so
stupid bro we haven't been driving this
car because it hasn't had brakes and I
literally had to stop driving it because
I was getting to a stop sign and it just
wasn't breaking I would have to put it
in neutral from really far and then it
would just stop and we just hit 130 not
wi of ass breaks
all right guys trade update right now it
is currently 6:36 in the afternoon like
you can see currently have about
$1,600 on the account so we're up
$22,000 the goal for this week was $900
and then the goal for next week was to
turn the $900 to about ,800 so we're
already ahead 2 weeks if I close this
trade right now and truthfully I might
let me show you guys right now the
market so exactly how I anticipated the
daily time frame has body closed under
this this previous structure point right
here so what I expect for price to do is
for price to then now for tomorrow this
Candlestick right here to have a
pullback into this area to then head to
the downside so we'll probably have a
wick pull back like that and then the
next day it will probably have then a
push to the downside like this now I
have to ask myself should I hold through
all that should I set and forget or
should I just close with where price is
right now because we're already ahead of
schedule but this trade without having
to add any more risk I can literally add
another, ,500 to the account with no
extra risk cuz the next trade that I
take I'm obviously exposing myself to
risk here I'm obviously positive so this
is what I'm predicting that the market
is going to do so this is obviously the
prediction so let me take this off and
then let me take this off this is what
it would look like on the 4 Hour the
4our would reest this line right here
which is the line on the daily time
frame that's just what it looks like on
the for hours that's this line is a
daily structure point so we can already
remove this because this already
happened to Perfection and what we would
be waiting for is for price to have a
pull back for here to then continue
selling down I don't know I'm going to
make up a decision probably in the next
like 30 45 minutes uh to see what I end
up doing but the other markets gbpusd
gbpusd currently we have had the
pullback not as far as we wanted to we
did have a push and in the daily time
frame we obviously had a push to the
downside I would have just wish this
came up a little bit further GBP CHF had
a beautiful bullish reaction and then
the next day we're having the retest
we're having the retest currently of
this resistance level being used as
support So if I were to close USD JPY at
this point where we are down here I
would probably enter this trade right
here because this is the one that's
ready the fastest and then euro gvp is
doing exactly as we wanted and it's
having that break right now and then all
we got to wait for now is this retest so
we already had this this break now we
just got to wait for this retest to then
sell so everything is literally playing
out to Perfection daily time frame has
body closed under like if you guys go to
literally last week's series you guys
can see how we waited all of last week
for price to pull back so last week
price was down here and then we waited 1
2 3 4 days for the price to pull back
and now 2 days of the reaction it'll
pull back to themselves so go watch last
week's series you guys can see that
we've been watching this pair already
for two weeks so for now currently up
about
$1,600 I'm going to make a decision very
soon to either set him forget or just
close it here and then we'll just add
another
[Music]
position you know I'm not even mad about
the [__] tickets I don't give a [__]
I take them I have you know an assistant
they take it to court I'm more pissed
off that the park is
closed so I just left the house to get a
[__] four this guy gave me four
different tickets he gave me one ticket
for not having my license on me
dismissed one ticket for not having a
license plate on the car dismissed one
ticket for not having proof of insurance
dismissed and then another one for
running the stop sign dismissed sorry
respectfully I love law enforcement I
respect my law
enforcement but none of that shit's
going to [__] none that's going to do
anything uh you know what I think that's
a little a bit of a payback revenge for
the from what we did earli what we did
earlier you know I rather have those
four tickets all day than the charge
of doing what we did earlier
today trade update we're currently up
we're up 1,900 so we're up actually
$2,300 so what we're going to do now is
go back home and I
guess [__] I don't know what to do right
now it's 9 it's 9:24 in the
afternoon we just fall asleep early and
then just play basketball early in the
morning but I think what we're going to
do now is probably just go
home [__] I don't know what to do what
do we do now
[Music]
[Applause]
our definition of going to sleep
early blood the on the Beamer yo I'm too
nasty at this [__] bro that is literally
no handbrake no [__] no break no
nothing no nothing just car bro there is
literally no angle kit no [__] um
clutch
nothing oh [__] the [__] tire though
damn oh my God straight up day so
currently we are looking
God damn wow bro
wow how long did it take you last year
to do this this is probably almost a
month last year that shows you how much
better of a Trader I've become I'm so
much less attached to the profits and of
the money behind this bro that's crazy
dude dude that's like brand new bro it's
not that bad piece of [__] Chinese tires
bro it's not that bad
it's not that
bad all right guys so I'm holding the
camera sa I fell asleep it is currently
12:32 at night I think you guys can see
it right there 12:32 at night and I just
got out the shower
and this is actually crazy the account
is currently sitting at
$3,000 [__] dollar this is crazy you
want know what's crazy I'm more excited
about these $3,000 in profit than I am
in like when I'm up 100 200k that's just
like boring this right here is so
exciting because you guys have literally
seen this go from $100 to the point
where it is right now let me show you
guys what the market has done right here
in the market you guys can see that the
market has had the push to then the
point where I said it was going to hit
the next structure point for the
takeprofit so bear with me I'm holding
the camera so you guys can see this is
the next takeprofit point that I said
that it was going to go to we've hit
that perfectly
gbpusd has had the push to the downside
then GBP CHF still kind of having the
retest and then your GBP is having the
pull back so we can enter another sell
at this point right here to then sell
we're just waiting on that so your GBP
is the next trade that I'm interested in
but USD JPY has been an absolute Beauty
so I'm going to wait these next 30
minutes for this Candlestick to close
you guys can see it has 30 minutes left
before it closes um before I actually
close this position on this Market but
actively right now exactly how we are
looking this is actively how we are
looking right now we up about $3,000
this insane so this is transparency to
its Finance you guys are seeing the
before the during the after pre-market
analysis absolutely
everything this challenge is becoming a
lot easier than I expected uh I'm more
confident than ever I'm not attached to
the money before I would have closed
this position because I'm like oh [__] I
don't want to lose out on the profits
for the week and just hit my profit for
the week now I'm just looking at the
charts and the charts are making the
money because the trades are simply
making sense so I'm just set of
forgetting following the set of forget
strategy
and I don't know I'm lost for words I'm
I'm excited it's about to be 1: in the
morning and I'm just looking at the
camera talking to myself and I don't
know I'm kind of using this moment to
like think back a little bit on the last
Challenge and the person that I was then
and I definitely was not ready to turn
$100 into a m even though yes I was a
millionaire and you know I was very
successful and I knew exactly what I was
doing I wasn't I wasn't prepared for it
and I think that's why I blew the
account but now come this time around I
can definitely see the kid that I was
back then and I believe that I am ready
for it now and I think my actions are
showing for it and it excit exites me
because I'm seeing the growth not so
much the money I can make a million
dollars in a month not a big deal but
it's more of the person who I've become
to normalize turning $100 into a million
with the skill set that I've Acquired
and how hard I've worked for this skill
set and the fact that it's literally
paying off so so well like I'm even
getting Goosebumps as I'm saying that
because there was a point where 5 years
ago I had nothing like none of this
trading stuff did anything for me other
than make me lose money fast forward now
it has built me a ginormous Community
like you guys watching this right now
has brought me a crazy lifestyle gotten
me a lot of
freedom and it's probably because I
never gave up so I just want to let you
guys know if you're going through any
rough moment or anything you know I've
been through there we've all been
through there and I can guarante [__]
tee you that it'll definitely be worth
it at the
end like I'm just sitting here in my
office 1:00 in the morning by myself and
it's moments like these where I really
kind of connect to the reality of the
situation of where my life is right now
and it's all because I never gave up and
because I believed in myself and I stuck
to one
thing so stick to one thing set and
[__]
forget all right guys trade update or
market update it is currently 9:00 in
the morning Wednesday morning so as you
guys can see we are current currently
obviously closed the position you guys
can see right here that the account is
at officially $3,000 you guys can see
here on my effects book pretty much uh
where we started the account with the
current balance updated two days ago you
guys can see here the history these are
all the trades that we have taken
obviously two trades on GBP JPY one
trade on USD JPY so last night I gave
you guys a little bit of a uh I don't
know I was like I was feeling good right
because the challenge is going very well
and really at night is when I get into
de really deep into my thoughts and just
look at this this is showing you guys
that following the trend is key so we
closed out the position yesterday right
here at this point I could have legit
continued to hold throughout this whole
entire position and I would have
probably made an extra, ,500 if I just
continued to set and forget this trade
would have given me a 1 to 10 risk to
reward if I would have simply done
nothing literally just set him forget
why because I'm trading with the trend
the trend is your friend and I'm trading
what the [__] hey SO trading with the
trend along with the S forget strategy
makes this so much easier but let's
still another trade update on gbpusd so
gbpusd we're waiting for the trade to
retest this structure level here
obviously we didn't make it we had to
push down and it looks like now we're
actually making our way up to that point
this is why you have to be patient and
wait for the trade to hit that area of
Interest GBP CHF we never got our entry
signal here on the retest if you notice
we had the break then on the retest no
bullish engulfing no trade loss avoided
this is why it's so important to have a
trading plan the set and forget trading
plan avoided this loss for tens of
thousands of traders in my Discord or
even on my Instagram where I post these
trades every single day and then lastly
is going to be Euro GBP and in Euro GBP
you guys can see how we literally had
perfectly the break then perfectly the
retest and then boom that engulfing
Candlestick that I continuously keep
talking about so this Market is actually
playing out exactly how I've been
anticipating I just obviously didn't
enter a position because we're already
in USD JPY and the goal for this week
was take $400 to 900 we took $400 to 3K
so we're definitely ahead of the ball
now I'm going to debate whether I take
more trades or not because honestly I
don't need the extra risk uh pretty much
done for the next I can L not trade for
the next two three weeks and I'm still
on schedule but if I do see a really
good opportunity I can't pass it up
because great opportunities in the
market don't come every single week they
can come every two three weeks so if the
opportunity is there you got to make
sure you capitalize off the trade that I
would be interested in taking would be
Euro GBP next if this gives me another
little bit of a pull back to around here
so I'm going to probably need a little
pull back like this probably to this
level so then head to the trade to the
downside my entry here stop loss around
here my take profit right around here
only way I'll take gbpusd is if we have
a pullback to this level to then sell
here we didn't make it so we got to wait
for it to make it basically what we're
waiting for here is
this so then
so with that being said
let's ah got actually almost
sneeze yo so last night we drifting the
Ferrari blew the tires we're drifting
the M3 blew the tires today we have no
more cars to drift but we got the ear
back all right guys trade up there right
now it's currently 7:00 Wednesday no new
trade going to do some cardio call it a
day
honestly forgot
hey 87 all right guys market update it
is currently Thursday morning 9:23 in
the morning yesterday after the
basketball just came chilled uh I think
I went out to eat it's pretty much it
currently the account is sitting at
exact
same $3,000 we have not taking any new
positions look how the market looks
gbpusd never made it back to this area
of interest and enter the cell so we
missed out on that trade USD JPY we this
loads had a big push to the downside now
where it looks like we're having that
retracement to the upside um this trade
has still ginormous potential to the
downside it has to have a really deep
pullback before actually continuing to
head down but I'm done with this trade
for this week when I hit a big trade
like this on a market I just cool done I
don't focus it on it until next week um
next is going to be GBP CHF so gbpchf we
were interested in buying all the way up
here and then the 4H hour really never
gave us our entry confirmation right
around here so we avoided this humongous
loss that we would have taken now this
is obviously giving us a left head and a
right shoulder so now we could wait for
the pull back into here to then sell to
enter a sell on gbpchf and then last but
not least is Euro GBP so we did have the
head and shoulders we did have the break
but then on this retest right here we
never had an engulfing Candlestick so we
did not take the trade that is the
importance of having a trading plan and
focusing and waiting on it you can wait
for a trade for 2 weeks for it to do
everything you wanted get to the area of
Interest break the area of Interest
retest it that can still take a week two
weeks three weeks and if at the end you
don't have your entry signal you don't
take your [__] trait that's exactly
what we did here we've been waiting for
this market for 2 weeks and it never
gave us our entry signal we did not take
the trade the first entry we missed it
which is fine which is this one right
here so we missed this first entry which
is dis bearish engulfing which actually
really good cuz we avoided the loss as a
whole but on the next entry we never got
the engulfing we don't take the tra we
got set and forget merch that we
actually got to go and ship right now
bro I saw a package here from Poland
Poland you know where Poland is in the
map we got to sell one of the shirts to
PO it's going just like this one time
don't forget so appreciate you guys that
buy the merch it's crazy I literally
make I think it's like $2 for a shirt I
literally charge you guys whatever I
make it for cuz it's more for Branding
don't really care to make money out
shirts these are actually being sent out
to you guys right now after we go do the
wire so all right guys trade update it
is
currently 10:28 in the afternoon so
today I haven't felt so good I ate
earlier in the morning
Oreo cereal for breakfast I haven't feel
like ass all day don't eat Oreos for
breakfast or Oreo cereal don't do it I
feel like I haven't even left the house
all day um wearing a hat my hair looks
crazy I'm trying to let it grow I'm
trying to look like Brad Pit when I like
slick it back I think I'm getting tired
of it I might take it all off I'm not
that patient letting my hair gr I like
looking fresh but tomorrow I getting a
haircut early in the morning but with
that being said straight update
currently 10:29 at night the account is
currently still exactly the same no
trades in the account as of right now
we're still at $3,000 so this is what
gbpusd looks like gbpusd obviously the
price didn't make it had to push to the
downside then USD JPY kind of pretty
much in the same spot as all day GBP CHF
obviously avoided the loss it's down
here and then Euro gvp just did not stop
at I completely decided to go to the
upside again no bearish engulfing no
entry signal no trade
so we're definitely up definitely up for
the week so the goal is 900 for the week
we're at 3,000 let's see if I can maybe
squeeze a little trade tonight probably
doubt it and um tomorrow we'll have a
little quick recap of what the week was
like and what we expect to do next week
I might decide tomorrow if we continue
to trade next week or if we just call it
a week for about 2 weeks and then we
just set and forget because we're about
two weeks ahead of schedule so again
make sure you guys tune in every single
Sunday we're going to be dropping these
series every single Sunday until I turn
$100 into a million but I'll update you
guys tomorrow in the morning all right
all right guys so market update it's
currently 10:21 in the morning Eric got
here a little late you know I don't know
why he got here a little late and
[__] so getting a haircut get a haircut
every single Friday Eric pulls up to the
house so soon as I'm done in about like
15 20 minutes I'll show you guys the
charts on how this week ended so give me
20 minutes well you guys are probably
just going to wait like 2 seconds all
right so before we do a market update
I'm going for a new hairstyle all right
don't roast my hairstyle something new
trying out with my barber let me know in
the comments below if you guys like the
new hairstyle or not I think I like it I
just feel like I look old as [__] what
do you who do you think that I look like
the bad guy from Harry Potter yeah I
don't know who the [__] that is pop up a
picture of him let me know if I look
like him let me know in the comments
below if you like the new hairstyle
don't play like a clown music or nothing
bro I think it looks dope right I think
it's like a new like slick back kind of
vibe obviously my hair's not long enough
for it yet feel like it makes me look
mature feel like I look like a young man
you know maybe I can actually hit the
100 to the mail now cuz I look like a
Wall Street dude look at me don't I look
like a Wall Street guy well half even
half course don't oh yeah you're right
the point is I'm I'm that guy now you
know what I'm saying all right so look
it say pop up a picture of me here with
bald head me right now and then me would
like the hair to the side let me know
which you would you guys like in the
comments below with that being said
let's do the recap of the week so before
we do the recap we start off the week
with
$437 and our goal for the end of this
week was to actually take it to
$900 now obviously this week we have
very clearly surpassed that and we are
currently saying sitting at
$3,074 on the account and this was all
done by taking one single trade but now
I'm going to show you all the markets
that we analyzed at the beginning of the
week how they played out which one's won
which one's lost and obviously which one
we ended up taking and actually before I
show you guys the charts let me show you
guys that we are in a real account
indeed so you guys can see right there
to the top left corner how it says real
account and then you guys can see the
account metrics and where we're
currently sitting at which is a total of
$3,074 so now with that being said let
me actually break down the exact markets
that we traded this week so we started
off the week with USD JPY which is the
winning trade that has given us the
$2,000 profit for this week very clearly
analized at the beginning of this week
this head and shoulders movement right
here and then we were entering right at
this retest got the engulfing setad of
forget now this Market went on for a lot
a lot longer because we are trading with
the trend so as you guys can see here on
the daily time frame clearly the daily
time frame went from bullish to then
bearish we're selling at a round
psychological level
157500 we had a daily EMA retest of
daily structure strong level of support
and resistance look how many different
things we had for this Market to go to
the downside and this is what I keep
repeating to you guys and my students
every single week when we analyze these
markets cuz I got on a car every single
Sunday with my students and I break down
these markets with them them where I
share them my top two top three trade
that I'm trading for the week if you
actually want to be part of those calls
with my students make sure you click the
link in the description below cuz I'm
sharing with them the trades that I'm
taking on this account with them live
before it happens every single week so
make sure you guys click the link in the
description below but I'm simply setting
up a scenario where it makes more sense
for this Market to sell rather than buy
and the goal should only be to look for
markets like these not look for any
other markets so USD GPI we got it you
guys can see very strong bearish
movements and then next week we're
probably going to be waiting for a
retest here to then sell which should be
a retest of this structure point and the
structure point which are obviously in
the same spot next is going to be gbpusd
at the beginning of the week we wanted
for price to have a pull back into this
area to then sell price quite did not
make it all the way up to that area as
you guys can see we missed it by a
couple Pips so we missed out on this
trade but the analysis did play out so
we have one winner which is USD JPY
gbpusd which technically would have been
winner but technically no trade GBP CHF
which we're waiting for a break and a
retest at this point to then head to the
upside we did not take it one because we
were already in the USD JPY cells and
two because we never got the entry
signal so a loss avoided we have one win
which is USD JPY one win that we just
missed and then one loss that we avoided
now the next Market is going to be Euro
GBP so Euro GBP we have the beautiful
Head and Shoulder ERS and then on this
comeback for the retest we never got our
entry confirmation at this point so we
avoided this loss completely so for this
week out of the four pairs that we
analyzed at the beginning of the week
one of them was a winner the other one
could have been a winner but we didn't
enter it and then we avoided two other
losses all you need to do is literally
be right half of the bance of time and
you're going to make money at the end of
the week every single week using the set
for Guess strategy and I think at the
beginning of the week we also mentioned
usdjpy for price to come back into this
level to then sell but obviously that
moved very very fast and we didn't end
up catching this trade Dam that's
[__] crazy because this is actually
the first trade that we took on the 100
to the mid account if I would have held
all the way down here wow I think i'
wouldd be at the milon already no I'm
okay so that's pretty much the recap of
the markets that we analyzed at the
beginning of the week if you guys want
to get these markets before they
actually happen and you guys want to
trade alongside with me you want to get
these same exact markets that I'm
trading on this 100 to the mail accounts
click the link in the description below
because I use my set and forget strategy
where I break down with my students
every single Sunday the markets that I'm
going to be trading for this challenge
in the week ahead so if you guys want to
be part of the 100 to the mill Challenge
and trade the same markets with me live
make sure you guys click the link in the
description below so you guys can join
the center forget Community you guys get
on the cards with me every single Sunday
ask me whatever questions you want or
any concerns you may have and I'm going
to be sharing with you these markets
before they even happen before any
everybody else sees them so that's how
I've been taking this $100 so far to
$3,000 so the goal for next week is
going to be to take $3,000 to $6,000 so
let's see how next week goes make sure
you guys hit that like And subscribe
button and tune in every single Sunday
because I'm only going to be uploading
turning $100 into a million until I
achieve the challenge of turning $100
into a million so expect a video just
like this one every single Sunday until
we achieve it appreciate you guys
watching this video all the way to the
end and I'll see you guys in the next
one